Hi, I'm Mii ko Sugunami, a.k.a. Mii, and Ogi Hana, a.k.a. Ogi Hana.
Today, we have something G, R, W, N...
Have you ever heard of it? I've heard "let's get ready together," but I've forgotten that English word.
I know, let's get ready together.
I just did the base. It's amazing to see only the base makeup done.
It's the most exciting part, so let's get to it.
Lately, I've been into mixing. Mixing?
The base is Biol's base. That's a really good text.
Snow and Gel Stuart. This is the new one.
I bought it because it has a higher SPF and is dustproof.
Wow, that's nice. It's a sunscreen, right?
And this is the one from Van. I have an image that I use it a lot.
Perfume makeup keepers. Nice.
I mix three of these together. You mix three?
It's like a milky lotion when you mix three together. That's amazing.
It makes the primer easy to rub on.
I also mix this perfume with the foundation afterwards.
Wow, that's really good. I put this on my skin.
I do. After the foundation.
Don't mix. Don't mix.
This time it was this way. This is Reel.
I don't wear primer these days. Oh, really?
Really? It doesn't fall apart afterwards.
Oh, shit. It doesn't fall apart.
So, bye-bye, bangs.
I'm going to clip it up.
I don't want the bangs to look like that, so I'm going to clip them from the base.
I'm doing it. Oh, really? That's great.
What do you do? Well, I have a theme to talk about today.
I was wondering if we could talk about the theme of the talk.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
What?
Oh, K-Palette's number 02.
This is really good.
It's the first one I've been able to buy recently.
02? Brown?
Yes. I got this from Mr. Neustein.
Neusteel? I think I got it from Neustei.
I use it a lot. I highly recommend it.
I'm growing my eyebrows now so that I can go to that eyebrow salon.
I'm growing them. I highly recommend the eyebrow salon because they really make your eyebrows kind of parallel.
I highly recommend it. If you're not sure, go for it.
How much can you do in a month? What, a month?
Midori is dyeing her hair.
It depends on the month, but I go twice a month.
It's hard when you dye your hair, isn't it? It's hard when you dye it.
But you know, I wonder how many girls dye their hair now?
Oh, that's right. Because Natsumi has blonde hair. That's right. I was so surprised.
I was so surprised. When we first saw her, we were all like, "What's that? Natsumi's all piled up.
Natsu-chan was dancing in the middle of her makeup,
She's always saying, "Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
I have an image of her saying that. Isn't Moemi beside you so fast?
So fast! You are very fast, aren't you?
I'd like to measure your makeup time.
Is she fast? I think she's filming her makeup too fast, right?
Yes, really.
The lame is always so cute. It's cute, isn't it? I want you to tell me.
The other day, I said to Kirari, "Isn't our makeup too light? I said something like that.
Then she said that my eyes might be too light.
I said, "Even if it's light, isn't it good to be pretty?
No, no, no, no, no, I wanted to give the impression that I was wearing makeup.
I want to show it. I want it to come out.
I want to show it.
We do all the live performances by ourselves,
Your technique is getting better and better.
It's getting better and better.
So, I want to make Maria's eyelashes, a lot.
But, you know, right now, there are times when I'm doing eyelashes and times when I'm not,
Now that I've taken a break from eyelashes, I'm not living at all.
Is that so?
But you know, it takes me so long to do my eyelashes.
I use tweezers.
Tweezers are great.
I pick them up with tweezers.
But the key is to put mascara on the tweezers and then pick them up.
I wonder if the makeup artist did the same thing.
Yes, something like that.
You should use tweezers.
It takes time.
It takes a lot of time, so I highly recommend it.
If you have time to spare, it's fine.
It's a little bit difficult.
I recommend it.
It's hard to say.
Oh, well, let's talk about work.
About work? That's a bit of a ruse.
No, I'm just... I have a top theme in front of me.
You've read about the top theme, haven't you?
I've read it,
More than the following, 2023 is 2days, enthusiasm, etc.
I don't know, I'm just...
I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure that wasn't the plan.
Oh no! I see!
There will be more than this 2023!
Two days!
Yes, it is!
That's so funny!
That's what I'm talking about!
But it's 2days this time!
What am I going to do! Muscle ache!
There!There!
That's it!
You see? But...
When I first started working with Fuchuki
I didn't think it would be an event that I would be able to do every year.
It's amazing.
I feel like I'm doing this every year, even though it's only once in my previous life.
And this time, it's summer!
In the middle of summer!
Summer!
I'm so happy! Oh, my gosh!
So great!
I think it will be easy for everyone to wear during the summer vacation.
That's for sure!
Come on everyone!
I'll be waiting for you!
Ta-da! Sparklers!
What?
You're early! It's almost over!
I have an image of Mire-chan being quick.
Makeup is done until the bangs come down.
The face is not complete until the bangs are down.
I know.
Hey, I know this is a bit of a tangent, but...
Chi-chan's makeup is so mature.
I know!
And your hair got longer.
It's crazy!
You gave me a great point.
Adult, what? Where was it?
She said she made sure to do her lower eyelashes properly.
You're so cute!
You're so mature.
Today is my first time using Lip Monster.
Lip Monster!
It said "only one per person".
There's a matte type and this regular type.
Both of them have less mokari.
Heh...
I have an image of Moe-chan using it a lot.
I know what you mean.
He uses it.
Isn't it good?
I only buy mascara from Hilk Touch.
Do you use it a lot?
I love it.
They use it a lot.
Where would you like to go?
Rome.
Lately I've been wanting to go to Rome, Italy.
What's in Rome?
It's just... it's an amazing city.
Is it?
I don't know... old buildings...
Pizza?
Pizza? Food?
Outside of pizza?
Sugar?
Do you know what sugar is?
I don't know.
It's like a building you look at.
Pizza?
Pizza!
What?
Pizza?
Pizza!
No, no, no, no.
What?
Pizza!
I see what you're getting at.
It's like a buzzer.
No, no, no, no.
Pizza!
I'm already laughing.
I just want to go see the pizza scale.
Rome is so beautiful.
The city is beautiful.
Yeah.
I think it's nice to have a purpose.
That's great.
Is there something you want to see?
Yeah.
I haven't told her.
You haven't?
Well, I've been wanting to go to Singapore.
I'd like to be in Singapore and feel like I'm in Singapore.
I see.
Like I'm in Singapore right now.
Hey, when you go to Singapore, call Hanae.
No, I can't.
Why not?
Because of the price.
Oh, you mean that?
It's included in the price.
Oh, really?Oh, really?
I don't know, I don't know.
But, you know, I want to go to Thailand.
I know, I want to go to Thailand.
Remember when Hii-chan was filming in Thailand?
So we should all go to Thailand with Hii-chan.
Pilgrimage?
Yes, a pilgrimage.
No way!
I want to go on a pilgrimage to a holy place.
Colored contacts...
What color contacts?
People keep asking me about them, so I brought a box.
What?
Here they are.
Hanane, I only use these.
Beam onesies.
It's marked with a monument to Tsubasa Honda.
What?
I get asked a lot about "Classy Beige.
I've only been using this for about 3 years now.
By the way, I'm Artiral Black.
Artiral?
Yes, it's called Artiral.
It's this one.
It's cute!
Oh, it matches my hair color.
Can I buy a lot of them? Crakon.
No, but...
About a year.
This one?
I don't know.
It's kind of stable with contacts, isn't it?
Stable.
I can't be adventurous.
I borrowed these earrings from Hanane.
And this necklace.
Necklace
I borrowed this from Hanane.
A fan gave it to me.
It's so cute!
Isn't it cute?
It is.
It's cute.
See you later.
So... did you enjoy getting ready with us?
I like to do my makeup while watching makeup videos.
You're welcome to join us.
Please subscribe to my channel and leave a comment.
That's all for now. That's all for now, this is Mirei Sugaya and Kogihana from Equal!
Bye bye!